onceuponatee.net 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | Once Upon a Tee

Privacy Policy

## **Privacy Policy**

Once Upon A Tee, LLC (“ **Once Upon A Tee** ” “ **us** ,” “ **we** ” or “ **our** ”) created this Privacy Policy in order to ensure the confidence of visitors (“ **you** ” or “ **your** ”) to [www.onceuponatee.net](http://www.onceuponatee.net/) (the “ **Site** ”), and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) is being used online. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your PII through this Site.

### **1\. Categories of Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”).**

Personal information is data that can be used to identify or contact a single person. We may collect the following types of information from you: 

  * Contact Data which includes your name, telephone number, mailing and email addresses,
  * Online Tracking information, which is described below;
  * Financial data (your credit card and related information); and
  * Demographic and additional information, which you provide to us by email, or by posting content or completing online forms or surveys.

###  ** ** **2\. Online Tracking.**

We collect Personal Information from you when you register on our Site or enter information on our Site, including subscribing to emails and/or newsletters.

We use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Site. These information gathering technologies are implemented by Shopify, whose Cookie Policy can be found here: <https://www.shopify.com/legal/cookies>. By way of example, some of these technologies capture your IP address, browser data and other information about your activity on our Site. Cookies enable us to keep track of your movement from page to page so you do not get asked for the same information you have already provided us. Cookies allow you to proceed through many pages of a site quickly and easily without having to authenticate or reprocess each new area you visit.

Our Site uses Shopify’s platform, and incorporates their Privacy Policy into ours for that purpose. You can access the Shopify privacy policy at <https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy>.

### **  3. Uses of Information Collected.**

We use Contact Data to contact you when necessary, which may include sending you periodic emails regarding your order or other products or services. All Contact Data is kept on third-party services operated by Mailchimp. Additional information regarding the privacy policies of the Mailchimp servers can be found here: _https://mailchimp.com/about/security/_.

We use information obtained from Online Tracking technologies (including information collected by our third party service providers) for web and email analytics and for marketing and advertising purposes. We currently use Google Analytics for these collection purposes, whose policies can be located here: _https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage_.

We also use Facebook pixel, whose policies can be found here: <https://www.facebook.com/business/a/facebook-pixel>. We may also use your information for internal purposes, such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and customer communications. We may also use your PII to personalize your user experience and allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

Payment information is not stored by the Site, but may be stored or otherwise used externally through any of our payment processors. Currently, we use three payment processors for processing payments through the Site: Stripe, PayPal, and Amazon Payments.

We may also use your information for internal purposes, such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and customer communications. We may also use your PII to personalize your user experience and allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

### **4.  Third Party Collection of Personally Identifiable Information.**

We approve third parties to collect Online Tracking information from the Site.  For example, Google or other advertisement providers may use Online Tracking, including to determine whether, when and for how long you view advertisements. 

### **5\. Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information.**

Except as otherwise provided in the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Contact Data private and will not share it with third parties, unless you choose to post it in a public forum on the Site or unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; (c) facilitate further development of the Site; or (d) enforce our Terms of Use. Your personal information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. 

### **6.  Secured Socket Layers.**

Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL, is an encryption technology that provides secure communications over the Internet. It does this by verifying that the server to which you are connected is actually the one it claims to be. It also encrypts all transactions between the parties communicating. Encryption is the scrambling of information as it is transmitted over the Internet to protect your confidentiality. Personal and credit card information passing between your computer and/or mobile device and many of our services is encrypted. This means that while your information is in transit it is scrambled so that only we can reassemble it in its original text format.  We use SSL protocol when secure communication with you is necessary.

### **7.  Lost or Stolen Information.**

You must promptly notify us if your user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission.  In such an event, we will cancel that account and assign you a new user name and password and update our records accordingly.

### **8.  Other Limits to Your Privacy.**

The Site may contain links to other websites and may approve other websites to obtain Online Tracking information from the Site.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.  When you post on the Site, the information that you disclose may become public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### **  9. CAN-SPAM Act.**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them.

 If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at unsubscribe@onceuponatee.net and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

### **10\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy.**

We reserve the right to change, update or modify this Privacy Policy. We will post all privacy policy changes and, if you have an account with us, we will notify you of any material change in our privacy policy.  Any such change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.  We will maintain prior versions of our Privacy Policy which will be available for your review.

Last updated: March 9, 2017
